datascience.com 2018-12-14

# Best Data Science Company | Top Data Science Companies | DataScience.com

DataScience.com has been [acquired](https://www.oracle.com/corporate/acquisitions/datascience/index.html) by Oracle and will soon transition to the Oracle Privacy Policy. Click [here](https://www.oracle.com/legal/privacy/index.html) to view the Oracle Privacy Policy.  Please note that the provisions of DataScience.com's Privacy Policy below will remain active until the policy transition is complete.

Your privacy is very important to us. Accordingly, we have developed this policy in order for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate, disclose, and make use of personal information. The following outlines our privacy policy:

  * Before or at the time of collecting personal information, we will identify the purposes for which information is being collected.
  * We will collect and use personal information solely with the objective of fulfilling those purposes specified by us and for other compatible purposes, unless we obtain the consent of the individual concerned or as required by law.
  * We will only retain personal information as long as necessary for the fulfillment of those purposes.
  * We will collect personal information by lawful and fair means and, where appropriate, with the knowledge or consent of the individual concerned.
  * Personal data should be relevant to the purposes for which it is to be used, and, to the extent necessary for those purposes, should be accurate, complete, and up-to-date.
  * We will protect personal information by reasonable security safeguards against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use, or modification.
  * We will make readily available to customers information about our policies and practices relating to the management of personal information. 

We are committed to conducting our business in accordance with these principles in order to ensure that the confidentiality of personal information is protected and maintained.
